<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Qiskit on SLC is</title><link>https://slc.is/tags/qiskit/</link><description>Recent content in Qiskit on SLC is</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://slc.is/tags/qiskit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quantum versus Avalanche Breakdown Randomness</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/comparerngs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/comparerngs/</guid><description>Avalanche breakdown and quantum are two methods for generating true random numbers. Here, we&amp;rsquo;ll compare them for feasibility and quality. The feasibility of a TRNG is how many bits per second it can produce while remaining random. And that leads us into quality which will be determined according to the NIST&amp;rsquo;s STS. We&amp;rsquo;ll also compare these methods against the computer&amp;rsquo;s default RNG as a baseline.
I&amp;rsquo;m using the Arcetri Team&amp;rsquo;s implementation of the STS.</description></item><item><title>Custom Gates in Qiskit with Pulse</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/customqiskitgates/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/customqiskitgates/</guid><description>Quantum research often requires applying operations in novel ways; however, it&amp;rsquo;s occasionally necessary to create gates to reduce circuit length. If too many operations are applied to a qubit, the quantum state is lost and no valuable insight can be gained. The quantum compiler can optimize these steps, but having the ability to create custom microwave pulses to apply to qubits is valuable.
In this quick tutorial, we will compose a Hadamard pulse and apply it to a qubit through a circuit using Qiskit.</description></item><item><title>Quantum Tales</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/quantumtales/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/quantumtales/</guid><description>Shortly after becoming an IBM Qiskit Advocate, I was introduced to the Unitary Fund. After writing a story where the reader uses Shor&amp;rsquo;s algorithm to decrypt a stock listing, I wanted to create more stories teaching quantum algorithms.
With the help of the Unitary Fund, I was able to realize this dream. I created a series of stories that teach various quantum algorithms. The stories are all rooted in classic fairy tales from around the world, except the protagonist now employees their quantum prowess to succeed.</description></item></channel></rss>