<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tools on SLC is</title><link>https://slc.is/tags/tools/</link><description>Recent content in Tools on SLC is</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://slc.is/tags/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chinese Word List</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/chinese/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/chinese/</guid><description>I used the SUBTLEX-CH frequency list to list the top 100 Chinese words per part of speech.
There are 2,683 words on this page. From rough estimates, this should cover 78% of spoken Mandarin. The lists are sorted first by total counts of each part of speech, then by the word itself. For example, verbs are the most common words in Mandarin, and the most common verb is &amp;ldquo;是&amp;rdquo;. So, the list begins with Verbs and its first entry is &amp;ldquo;是&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Generating a PGP Key</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/pgp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/pgp/</guid><description>This is an extreme guide to generating a PGP key. A simple tutorial will suffice; however, this will help generate the most secure key possible.
Quantum Background The NIST compared the security of RSA and ECC keys and concluded that, with sufficient lengths in key complexity, either standard will suffice.
Shor&amp;rsquo;s algorithm factors coprime numbers, thus is able to recreate the private key to any RSA-generated public key. This NIST paper, however, asserts that Grover&amp;rsquo;s algorithm can be used to recreate the private key to any ECC-generated public key.</description></item><item><title>RGB for Average Contrast</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/averagergb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/averagergb/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on an interpreted assembly-like language called Bee Assembly, and the editor&amp;rsquo;s background will change from a light or dark color depending on the user&amp;rsquo;s preference. It uses Simple.css to style the page, so I wanted to avoid adding additional CSS rules. Instead, I opted to find the best red, green, and blue values to maximize the contrast between the white and black backgrounds, and the text. I also found the average gray value.</description></item><item><title>My First Car</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/firsttruck/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/firsttruck/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always been curious about how to repair cars since debugging tends to follow similar thought processes. Today, I finally got my first car, a 1988 Toyota Pickup affectionately known as Lil&amp;rsquo; Mo. I&amp;rsquo;m excited to learn how to work on its famous 22R-E engine and handle wiring for the electronics.
Music is my biggest priority after safety, so having a bangin&amp;rsquo; stereo is a must. After that, the appearance of the truck is important since I tend to get smiles or thumbs up when driving it.</description></item><item><title>Exploring Privacy Tools</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/privacytools/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/privacytools/</guid><description>The brain has been hacked and its security patches come slowly. In order to avoid targeted ads and refining my digital consciousness, I&amp;rsquo;m making steady progress toward respectful technology.
After learning more about AI, I began to understand the importance of privacy. Everyone has their own reasons for protecting their data, and mine is to reduce the ability of models to fit me. This ties into preventing ad recommendations and other popular motivations broadly, but I doubt we understand the implications of modelling human behavior.</description></item><item><title>Creating My Site</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/creatingmysite/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/creatingmysite/</guid><description>I bought my first domain through Google Domains and actually hosted my site through Google&amp;rsquo;s website builder. It really is a great free builder with solid SEO, but I&amp;rsquo;m a programmer, so I wanted to program.
Distributed networks are an amazing technology, and I was drawn to IPFS hosting. I used Pinata to pin my new site, but when I tried using an HTTP request for a different page, it failed.</description></item><item><title>Tools For Writing</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/writingtools/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/writingtools/</guid><description>Half a year ago, I began the process of writing my first book. This book is special to me because it attempts to teach middle schoolers and those without experience, quantum. By using fairy tales everyone is familiar with, it is easier to teach new topics. I found that younger audiences were able to learn new material better when that knowledge was introduced in the context of popular stories. In this way, I will use stories from around the world to help teach many people the basics of quantum and inspire them to learn more.</description></item></channel></rss>