<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Privacy on SLC is</title><link>/tags/privacy/</link><description>Recent content in Privacy on SLC is</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/privacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Generating a PGP Key</title><link>/posts/pgp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/pgp/</guid><description>This is an extreme guide to generating a PGP key. A simple tutorial will suffice; however, this will help generate the most secure key possible.
Quantum Background The NIST compared the security of RSA and ECC keys and concluded that, with sufficient lengths in key complexity, either standard will suffice.
Shor&amp;rsquo;s algorithm factors coprime numbers, thus is able to recreate the private key to any RSA-generated public key. This NIST paper, however, asserts that Grover&amp;rsquo;s algorithm can be used to recreate the private key to any ECC-generated public key.</description></item><item><title>Delete Me Guides</title><link>/posts/deletemeguides/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/deletemeguides/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m going to create a simple program that will delete personal information like deleteme. It&amp;rsquo;ll be open-source and able to run whenever you please. I&amp;rsquo;ll use the guides from deleteme to help identify services and their links.
I have each link listed below, but you can run the code below to download every document.
Guide Links: https://joindeleteme.com/help/kb/how-to-national-do-not-call-registry/ https://joindeleteme.com/help/kb/how-to-remove-yourself-from-alc/ https://joindeleteme.com/help/kb/how-to-remove-yourself-from-allbiz/ https://joindeleteme.com/help/kb/how-to-remove-yourself-from-ancestry/ https://joindeleteme.com/help/kb/how-to-remove-yourself-from-arrestfacts/ https://joindeleteme.com/help/kb/how-to-remove-yourself-from-background-checks-com/ https://joindeleteme.com/help/kb/how-to-remove-yourself-from-california-notaries/ https://joindeleteme.com/help/kb/how-to-remove-yourself-from-checkpeople-com/ https://joindeleteme.com/help/kb/how-to-remove-yourself-from-clustrmaps/ https://joindeleteme.com/help/kb/how-to-remove-yourself-from-criminal-screen/ https://joindeleteme.com/help/kb/how-to-remove-yourself-from-criminal-watch-dog/ https://joindeleteme.com/help/kb/how-to-remove-yourself-from-criminalpages-com/ https://joindeleteme.</description></item><item><title>Exploring Privacy Tools</title><link>/posts/privacytools/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/privacytools/</guid><description>The brain has been hacked and its security patches come slowly. In order to avoid targeted ads and refining my digital consciousness, I&amp;rsquo;m making steady progress toward respectful technology.
After learning more about AI, I began to understand the importance of privacy. Everyone has their own reasons for protecting their data, and mine is to reduce the ability of models to fit me. This ties into preventing ad recommendations and other popular motivations broadly, but I doubt we understand the implications of modelling human behavior.</description></item><item><title>Testing DuckDuckGo's Email</title><link>/posts/pentestddg/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/pentestddg/</guid><description>DuckDuckGo began releasing @duck.com emails. These emails are currently in beta and only act as an email-forwarding account. The purpose of this post is to stess-test the service and see where it earns the beta tag.
Duck.com vs. Duck.co Both duck.com and duck.co forward to duckduckgo.com, so I wondered if a duck.com and duck.co email forward emails identically as well. When I tried emailing spence@duck.co, however, I received the following 550 error:</description></item><item><title>Every Bang in DuckDuckGo</title><link>/posts/ddgbangs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/ddgbangs/</guid><description>In response to a question about a list of all DuckDuckGo !bangs, I wrote this script:
from requests import get from json import loads def get_bangs(): r = get(&amp;#39;https://duckduckgo.com/bang.v260.js&amp;#39;) r = loads(r.text) return r def create_dict(bangs): d = {&amp;#39;Misc&amp;#39;: set()} for i in bangs: el = (i[&amp;#39;s&amp;#39;].strip(), i[&amp;#39;t&amp;#39;].strip()) try: if i[&amp;#39;c&amp;#39;] in d: d[i[&amp;#39;c&amp;#39;]].add(el) else: d[i[&amp;#39;c&amp;#39;]] = set(el) except: d[&amp;#39;Misc&amp;#39;].</description></item><item><title>The Best TLD is Not .com</title><link>/posts/tlds/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/tlds/</guid><description>The TLD is controlled by its parent company or country. When choosing a TLD, consider the site to be strictly under the laws of the country that ultimate controls it. For example, if you use a .ae domain, with a single query from the monarchy, your site could be completely removed. On the otherhand, if you use a domain from… well let&amp;rsquo;s get into it 😉
The EFF outlined a comparison of TLDs.</description></item></channel></rss>