<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Quantum on SLC is</title><link>/categories/quantum.html</link><description>Recent content in Quantum on SLC is</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/quantum/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Generating a PGP Key</title><link>/posts/pgp.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/pgp.html</guid><description>This is an extreme guide to generating a PGP key. A simple tutorial will suffice; however, this will help generate the most secure key possible.
Quantum Background The NIST compared the security of RSA and ECC keys and concluded that, with sufficient lengths in key complexity, either standard will suffice.</description></item><item><title>Degrees of Randomness and the Law of Large Numbers</title><link>/posts/randomness.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/randomness.html</guid><description>In a previous post comparing quantum and avalanche diode methods of true random number generation, an interesting pattern emerged. The quantum random numbers would pass more STS tests than avalanche diode random numbers. Seemingly, the quantum RNG converges to a mean before the diode RNG.</description></item><item><title>Quantum versus Avalanche Breakdown Randomness</title><link>/posts/comparerngs.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/comparerngs.html</guid><description>Avalanche breakdown and quantum are two methods for generating true random numbers. Here, we&amp;rsquo;ll compare them for feasibility and quality. The feasibility of a TRNG is how many bits per second it can produce while remaining random. And that leads us into quality which will be determined according to the NIST&amp;rsquo;s STS.</description></item><item><title>Custom Gates in Qiskit with Pulse</title><link>/posts/customqiskitgates.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/customqiskitgates.html</guid><description>Quantum research often requires applying operations in novel ways; however, it&amp;rsquo;s occasionally necessary to create gates to reduce circuit length. If too many operations are applied to a qubit, the quantum state is lost and no valuable insight can be gained.</description></item><item><title>Quantum Physics I</title><link>/posts/quantumphysics.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/quantumphysics.html</guid><description>I began learning quantum mechanics with Professor Allan Adams on MIT OpenCourseWare! This will be an ongoing post about interesting things I learn, as a way to share a computer scientist&amp;rsquo;s perspective on quantum physics as well as to hold myself accountable in finishing the course.</description></item><item><title>Summer of Quantum</title><link>/posts/quantumsummer.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/quantumsummer.html</guid><description>This summer will be affectionately known as the Quantum Summer.
Because of a scheduling mishap, I found myself teaching three quantum courses at once:
Brookhaven National Laboratory Qiskit Global Summer School QuBes Camp This situation pushed me to balance responsibilities and make tons of quantum resources.</description></item><item><title>Quantum Tales</title><link>/posts/quantumtales.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/quantumtales.html</guid><description>Shortly after becoming an IBM Qiskit Advocate, I was introduced to the Unitary Fund. After writing a story where the reader uses Shor&amp;rsquo;s algorithm to decrypt a stock listing, I wanted to create more stories teaching quantum algorithms.
With the help of the Unitary Fund, I was able to realize this dream.</description></item></channel></rss>