<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Artificial Intelligence on SLC is</title><link>/categories/artificial-intelligence.html</link><description>Recent content in Artificial Intelligence on SLC is</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Assembly Neural Network on Pico</title><link>/posts/assemblypico.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/assemblypico.html</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the Raspberry Pi Foundation&amp;rsquo;s products for almost a decade now, but they only recently released their first microcontroller. Their custom RP2040 has an ARM Cortex-M0+ chip that, obviously, uses ARM assembly. I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to learn assembly and this is definitely a great opportunity to do so.</description></item><item><title>Neural Networks From Scratch</title><link>/posts/nnfs.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/nnfs.html</guid><description>The best way to learn how something works is to build it from scratch. Unsurprisingly, the Neural Networks from Scratch book does exactly that.
I had the privilege to edit it alongside Harrison and Daniel, and wanted to write about my experiences editing a technical book.</description></item><item><title>Poems</title><link>/posts/poems.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/poems.html</guid><description>Alexandre Alexandre, my trembling wings.
Your dead are in the fields.
Our fight was stretched on the forest.
A wealth of shadow lies beneath the woodland hills.
An earth that is not mine.
Skies A sky became a wave,
and suddenly the breeze -</description></item><item><title>IB CS Extended Essay</title><link>/posts/ee.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/ee.html</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;How feasible are deep neural networks in generating thematically diverse video game music?&amp;rdquo;
Introduction Research The purpose of this paper is to test the ability of deep neural networks (DNNs), using long short-term memory architecture to model video game (VG) music and evaluate its aptitude in expressing thematically diverse emotion.</description></item><item><title>Raspberry Pi and Caenorhabditis Elegans</title><link>/posts/wormpi.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/wormpi.html</guid><description>One of my first projects was AI projects was taking the OpenWorm C. Elegans brain map and connecting it to a Raspberry Pi. The Pi was integrated with Lego Mindstorms, so the Lego motors would move in the direction the worm wanted to go.</description></item></channel></rss>