<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Artificial Intelligence on SLC is</title><link>https://slc.is/categories/artificial-intelligence/</link><description>Recent content in Artificial Intelligence on SLC is</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://slc.is/categories/artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Assembly Neural Network on Pico</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/assemblypico/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/assemblypico/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the Raspberry Pi Foundation&amp;rsquo;s products for almost a decade now, but they only recently released their first microcontroller. Their custom RP2040 has an ARM Cortex-M0+ chip that, obviously, uses ARM assembly. I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to learn assembly and this is definitely a great opportunity to do so.
The goal is to code a very basic neural network in assembly.
I want to make a simple neural network, and luckily the Pico has a multiplication instruction (unlike the 6502 processor).</description></item><item><title>Neural Networks From Scratch</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/nnfs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/nnfs/</guid><description>The best way to learn how something works is to build it from scratch. Unsurprisingly, the Neural Networks from Scratch book does exactly that.
I had the privilege to edit it alongside Harrison and Daniel, and wanted to write about my experiences editing a technical book.
On January 10th, 2020, Harrison, or sentdex, released a YouTube video announcing a Kickstarter campaign for funding Neural Networks From Scratch. On January 10th, I backed the Kickstarter 😂 This was the first time I would formally edit something, as well try my hand at understanding the inner workings of neural networks.</description></item><item><title>Poems</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/poems/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/poems/</guid><description>Alexandre Alexandre, my trembling wings.
Your dead are in the fields.
Our fight was stretched on the forest.
A wealth of shadow lies beneath the woodland hills.
An earth that is not mine.
Skies A sky became a wave,
and suddenly the breeze -
azure floating on the hills.
Our music was not of a god or spirit, not of that colour of the sea.
falafel My falafel from the seas and palm-trees.</description></item><item><title>IB CS Extended Essay</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/ee/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/ee/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;How feasible are deep neural networks in generating thematically diverse video game music?&amp;rdquo;
Introduction Research The purpose of this paper is to test the ability of deep neural networks (DNNs), using long short-term memory architecture to model video game (VG) music and evaluate its aptitude in expressing thematically diverse emotion. In other words, how feasible are deep neural networks in generating thematic video game music? My goal is to test whether a DNN can compose engaging music capable of accentuating themes presented in video games.</description></item><item><title>Raspberry Pi and Caenorhabditis Elegans</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/wormpi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/wormpi/</guid><description>One of my first projects was AI projects was taking the OpenWorm C. Elegans brain map and connecting it to a Raspberry Pi. The Pi was integrated with Lego Mindstorms, so the Lego motors would move in the direction the worm wanted to go.
# BrickPi3 Worm Brain # Written by Spencer Churchill 2016, in Python 2.7 # The BrickPi3 Worm Brain uses a Postsynaptic dictionary based on the C Elegans Connectome Model # This application can be ran on the Raspberry Pi BrickPi robot with an ultrasonic sensor that represents Nose Touch when activated from BrickPi import * import time BrickPiSetup() # setup the serial port for communication BrickPi.</description></item></channel></rss>