<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Thoughts on SLC is</title><link>/categories/thoughts.html</link><description>Recent content in Thoughts on SLC is</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Meanest Color</title><link>/posts/meancolor.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/meancolor.html</guid><description>Have you ever wanted to know what the most mean color is? Red might come to mind — a fiery and belligerent color. But I&amp;rsquo;ll do one better! I&amp;rsquo;ll give you the color vector that&amp;rsquo;s closest to every other color vector.</description></item><item><title>My First Car</title><link>/posts/firsttruck.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/firsttruck.html</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always been curious about how to repair cars since debugging tends to follow similar thought processes. Today, I finally got my first car, a 1988 Toyota Pickup affectionately known as Lil&amp;rsquo; Mo. I&amp;rsquo;m excited to learn how to work on its famous 22R-E engine and handle wiring for the electronics.</description></item><item><title>Delete Me Guides</title><link>/posts/deletemeguides.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/deletemeguides.html</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m going to create a simple program that will delete personal information like deleteme. It&amp;rsquo;ll be open-source and able to run whenever you please. I&amp;rsquo;ll use the guides from deleteme to help identify services and their links.
I have each link listed below, but you can run the code below to download every document.</description></item><item><title>Minecraft Seeds</title><link>/posts/minecraftseeds.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/minecraftseeds.html</guid><description>Title Screen: Version: Beta 1.7.3 Seed: 2151901553968352745 or 8091867987493326313 Player X: 61.48 Player Y: 75 Player Z: -68.73 Pack.png: Version: Alpha 1.2.2 [Java] Seed: 3257840388504953787 Player X: 116 Player Y: -31 Skull on Fire: Version: Alpha 1.1.2_01 [Java] Seed: -1044887956651363087 or -6984854390176336655 Player X: -249.</description></item><item><title>Short and Sweet Google Interview Process</title><link>/posts/googleinterview.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/googleinterview.html</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ll use this post as a progress report of the Google Internship application process. The only unique thing I did in regards with the initial application was specifying my interest in the ChromeOS team. In addition, I submitted a bug report to the ChromeOS team and mentioned my application.</description></item><item><title>QR Quine</title><link>/posts/qrquine.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/qrquine.html</guid><description>I was hoping to encode the b64 string of a QR code into another QR code. The catch was that the encoded QR code would match the encoded string of the QR code. When you scan the QR code, it would return itself.</description></item><item><title>The Last Single-Letter Domain</title><link>/posts/lastis.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/lastis.html</guid><description>ý.is is now taken. This morning, I began rummaging through the NCIS&amp;rsquo; Domain Rules and found a list of all allowed single characters.
a b c d e f g h i j k l m n o p q r s t u v w x y z - 0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 á æ é í ð ó ö ú ý þ After a few searches and CAPTCHAs, I was surprised to that ý was available!</description></item><item><title>Searching for Interactive Code</title><link>/posts/runcode.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/runcode.html</guid><description>I want readers to execute code I use anywhere in my blog. Recently, I added code that scrapes DuckDuckGo&amp;rsquo;s !bangs; however, the reader would need to run the code on their own machine. It&amp;rsquo;d be helpful if they could have executable code embedded in the post.</description></item><item><title>Exploring Privacy Tools</title><link>/posts/privacytools.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/privacytools.html</guid><description>The brain has been hacked and its security patches come slowly. In order to avoid targeted ads and refining my digital consciousness, I&amp;rsquo;m making steady progress toward respectful technology.
After learning more about AI, I began to understand the importance of privacy.</description></item><item><title>Testing DuckDuckGo's Email</title><link>/posts/pentestddg.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/pentestddg.html</guid><description>DuckDuckGo began releasing @duck.com emails. These emails are currently in beta and only act as an email-forwarding account. The purpose of this post is to stess-test the service and see where it earns the beta tag.
Duck.com vs. Duck.co Both duck.</description></item><item><title>The Best TLD is Not .com</title><link>/posts/tlds.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/tlds.html</guid><description>The TLD is controlled by its parent company or country. When choosing a TLD, consider the site to be strictly under the laws of the country that ultimate controls it. For example, if you use a .ae domain, with a single query from the monarchy, your site could be completely removed.</description></item><item><title>Grokking Go</title><link>/posts/grokkinggo.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/grokkinggo.html</guid><description>Despite an earlier post being so optimistic about the IPFS, I decided to self-host this site. I&amp;rsquo;m only leaving IPFS because this site will never be popular enough to be on any node besides my own. In this way, I was already hosting from the start.</description></item><item><title>Summer of Quantum</title><link>/posts/quantumsummer.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/quantumsummer.html</guid><description>This summer will be affectionately known as the Quantum Summer.
Because of a scheduling mishap, I found myself teaching three quantum courses at once:
Brookhaven National Laboratory Qiskit Global Summer School QuBes Camp This situation pushed me to balance responsibilities and make tons of quantum resources.</description></item><item><title>Tools For Writing</title><link>/posts/writingtools.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/writingtools.html</guid><description>Half a year ago, I began the process of writing my first book. This book is special to me because it attempts to teach middle schoolers and those without experience, quantum. By using fairy tales everyone is familiar with, it is easier to teach new topics.</description></item><item><title>Future of Blockchain Domains</title><link>/posts/blockchain.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/blockchain.html</guid><description>I bought this domain (splch.zil) today! I have a .dev/net domain, but I don&amp;rsquo;t like the idea of renting a space. When I discovered blockchain domain names and IPFS hosting, I knew it suited me.
It all depends on security and privacy Now, I don&amp;rsquo;t know what the future holds for blockchain and IPFS internet, but I think that the importance of publicly served domains will increase by considering present privacy trends.</description></item><item><title>Converting Country Codes to Flag Emojis</title><link>/posts/flag2emoji.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/flag2emoji.html</guid><description>In a Flutter app I started — and eventually stopped — working on, I was converting country codes to their corresponding flag emojis in Dart. This was a fun problem to solve and it&amp;rsquo;s actually my highest rated solution on</description></item><item><title>Poems</title><link>/posts/poems.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/poems.html</guid><description>Alexandre Alexandre, my trembling wings.
Your dead are in the fields.
Our fight was stretched on the forest.
A wealth of shadow lies beneath the woodland hills.
An earth that is not mine.
Skies A sky became a wave,
and suddenly the breeze -</description></item><item><title>M-Protect</title><link>/posts/m-protect.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/m-protect.html</guid><description>M-Protect, the virus protector that promised everything and fulfilled nothing, was an overnight sensation. After amassing a cult following of thirteen-year-olds and becoming the sponsor of the school&amp;rsquo;s crossfire tournament, this antivirus program was seemingly on the up and up.</description></item></channel></rss>