<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Math on SLC is</title><link>https://slc.is/categories/math/</link><description>Recent content in Math on SLC is</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://slc.is/categories/math/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Meanest Color</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/meancolor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/meancolor/</guid><description>Have you ever wanted to know what the most mean color is? Red might come to mind — a fiery and belligerent color. But I&amp;rsquo;ll do one better! I&amp;rsquo;ll give you the color vector that&amp;rsquo;s closest to every other color vector.
Here, the most average and mean color can be determined with word2vec and vector averaging.
Process Load the word2vec model Load the list of colors Sum the vectors of each color together Divide by the number of colors Find the color vector with the largest cosine similarity to that vector Python pip install gensim import numpy import gensim.</description></item><item><title>Generating a PGP Key</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/pgp/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/pgp/</guid><description>This is an extreme guide to generating a PGP key. A simple tutorial will suffice; however, this will help generate the most secure key possible.
Quantum Background The NIST compared the security of RSA and ECC keys and concluded that, with sufficient lengths in key complexity, either standard will suffice.
Shor&amp;rsquo;s algorithm factors coprime numbers, thus is able to recreate the private key to any RSA-generated public key. This NIST paper, however, asserts that Grover&amp;rsquo;s algorithm can be used to recreate the private key to any ECC-generated public key.</description></item><item><title>RGB for Average Contrast</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/averagergb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/averagergb/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on an interpreted assembly-like language called Bee Assembly, and the editor&amp;rsquo;s background will change from a light or dark color depending on the user&amp;rsquo;s preference. It uses Simple.css to style the page, so I wanted to avoid adding additional CSS rules. Instead, I opted to find the best red, green, and blue values to maximize the contrast between the white and black backgrounds, and the text. I also found the average gray value.</description></item><item><title>Degrees of Randomness and the Law of Large Numbers</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/randomness/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/randomness/</guid><description>In a previous post comparing quantum and avalanche diode methods of true random number generation, an interesting pattern emerged. The quantum random numbers would pass more STS tests than avalanche diode random numbers. Seemingly, the quantum RNG converges to a mean before the diode RNG.
This should not be the case since both methods produce true random numbers, so this post will be exploring if this is actually occurring and why.</description></item><item><title>Quantum Physics I</title><link>https://slc.is/posts/quantumphysics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/posts/quantumphysics/</guid><description>I began learning quantum mechanics with Professor Allan Adams on MIT OpenCourseWare! This will be an ongoing post about interesting things I learn, as a way to share a computer scientist&amp;rsquo;s perspective on quantum physics as well as to hold myself accountable in finishing the course.
The miracle is not that electrons behave oddly. The miracle is that when you take $10^{26}$ electrons, they behave like cheese! 🧀
The first lecture taught me something fundamental about the term superposition.</description></item></channel></rss>