<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Math on SLC is</title><link>/categories/math.html</link><description>Recent content in Math on SLC is</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/math/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Data-Driven Keyboard</title><link>/posts/fwuzix.html</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/fwuzix.html</guid><description>Using the keystrokes and blog authorship datasets, we can derive a keyboard that is optimized for the shortest delays between the most common key presses. For example, if x to q has the shortest delay of 33ms, but t to h is the most frequently occurring key presses, then we can replace x with t and q with h.</description></item><item><title>The Meanest Color</title><link>/posts/meancolor.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/meancolor.html</guid><description>Have you ever wanted to know what the most mean color is? Red might come to mind — a fiery and belligerent color. But I&amp;rsquo;ll do one better! I&amp;rsquo;ll give you the color vector that&amp;rsquo;s closest to every other color vector.</description></item><item><title>Generating a PGP Key</title><link>/posts/pgp.html</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/pgp.html</guid><description>This is an extreme guide to generating a PGP key. A simple tutorial will suffice; however, this will help generate the most secure key possible.
Quantum Background The NIST compared the security of RSA and ECC keys and concluded that, with sufficient lengths in key complexity, either standard will suffice.</description></item><item><title>RGB for Average Contrast</title><link>/posts/averagergb.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/averagergb.html</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m working on an interpreted assembly-like language called Bee Assembly, and the editor&amp;rsquo;s background will change from a light or dark color depending on the user&amp;rsquo;s preference. It uses Simple.css to style the page, so I wanted to avoid adding additional CSS rules.</description></item><item><title>Degrees of Randomness and the Law of Large Numbers</title><link>/posts/randomness.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/randomness.html</guid><description>In a previous post comparing quantum and avalanche diode methods of true random number generation, an interesting pattern emerged. The quantum random numbers would pass more STS tests than avalanche diode random numbers. Seemingly, the quantum RNG converges to a mean before the diode RNG.</description></item><item><title>Quantum Physics I</title><link>/posts/quantumphysics.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/quantumphysics.html</guid><description>I began learning quantum mechanics with Professor Allan Adams on MIT OpenCourseWare! This will be an ongoing post about interesting things I learn, as a way to share a computer scientist&amp;rsquo;s perspective on quantum physics as well as to hold myself accountable in finishing the course.</description></item></channel></rss>