<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Go on SLC is</title><link>https://slc.is/tags/go/</link><description>Recent content in Go on SLC is</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://slc.is/tags/go/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Grokking Go</title><link>https://slc.is/archive/grokking-go/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://slc.is/archive/grokking-go/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://slc.is/images/gocert.webp" alt="Featured image of post Grokking Go" />&lt;p>Despite an &lt;a class="link" href="https://slc.is/#Future%20of%20Blockchain%20Domains" >earlier post&lt;/a> being so optimistic about the &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->IPFS&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->, I decided to self-host this site. I&amp;rsquo;m only leaving IPFS because this site will never be popular enough to be on any node besides my own. In this way, I was already hosting from the start. It all began as a fun endeavor to apply Go, but has since led to a &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/splch/google-go-coursera" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>certificate&lt;/a> and obsessive refinement of the &lt;a class="link" href="https://observatory.mozilla.org/analyze/slc.is" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>server&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Most recently, I have added the ability to edit and create posts from within this site! There&amp;rsquo;s quite a bit going on in the server&amp;hellip; particularly in one file 😳, so I should look into splitting the code into separate files: one for setting up the server, and another for parsing the markdown.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I am really enjoying Go, though. I&amp;rsquo;m more comfortable with interpreted languages as Python was my first; however, I am quickly converting to a statically-typed fan! Also, this is my first post using the new website editor 🤪&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This is the code for my Go server hosted on Replit. &lt;a class="link" href="https://replit.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Replit&lt;/a> makes for an easy hosting provider, as well. I can make updates quickly without worrying about power outages causing the site to go down. Initially, I was using the &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->gzip&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --> package from Go&amp;rsquo;s standard library, but audio couldn&amp;rsquo;t be decoded. I opted to use the package by the New York Times instead. The server configuration is primarily based on three sources: &lt;a class="link" href="https://blog.cloudflare.com/exposing-go-on-the-internet/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Cloudflare&lt;/a>, &lt;a class="link" href="https://ssl-config.mozilla.org/#server=go&amp;amp;version=1.16.7&amp;amp;config=intermediate&amp;amp;guideline=5.6" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Mozilla&lt;/a>, and their &lt;a class="link" href="https://observatory.mozilla.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>observatory&lt;/a> tool.&lt;/p>
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --></description></item></channel></rss>